All right. Good. No. Um, good day. Two
really good football players. Um, young,
both are young. Um, productive.
CJ, you know, we
we've liked CJ through the whole
process. He stands for all the right
stuff. Um, he's an athletic, fast mic.
He'll be a green dot guy for us from the
get-go. I mean, he's a face of the
program type of guy. He's a really
special dude. now loves to play, serious
about football. Um, it's evident when
you watch Georgia tape. I mean, he shows
up and look, I mean, Kirby and Kirby and
Will both, you know, Mus Champamp who's
been a friend a long time, like they
couldn't they were ausive
in what kind of player this kid is. So,
and it's a good fit, you know, for us.
Um, and then AJ is, you know, AJ's an
interesting, he's an interesting guy,
and and what I love the most is, you
know, especially in the transfer world,
but goes to New Mexico, starts, goes to
Houston, starts, goes to LSU, starts,
um, takes the ball away. He's physical.
Um, no, he he's going to be a good
addition. We think we got younger and
faster on defense.
>> Is he a box guy?
>> I I don't quite see it that way. I mean,
I know that was getting thrown out
there. Um, no, we think he can play down
and, you know, in in the middle of the
field.
>> When you looked at the when you got the
trade off where you were able to pick
the fourth round pick, was that one of
the goals coming in?
>> Yeah, and we almost did it again, but,
you know, we were just at a point with
CJ, we just we didn't want to lose him.
We'd already kind of played with fire
once when we moved back and our
analytics team, Greg, and them do a
great job kind of where guys are going
to go and target. We thought we could
kick back and still get him. um just
didn't want to play. We had one more
chance and we're like, "Nah, let's don't
chance it." But no, the chance to get
another four tomorrow. Now we got six
picks tomorrow, which is good. Um that
was important.
>> AJ, um you talked about transfer. Do you
appreciate that pretty much everywhere
he went, he tried to get to a higher
level and more responsibility, more
competition, that sort of thing?
>> Just played good at everywhere he's
been. I mean, like at every level, like
I mean, every school he went to, he
played well. Um,
and that's a like to be able to adjust
and and on the, you know, when you when
you're a transfer now, I mean, it is a
little like being a, you know, getting
cut in our league or free free agent in
our league, you change teams
automatically and he go in and you keep
performing. I mean, that's a that's a
good quality to have. Like, he's able to
handle chaos and change and still
perform. That's a good thing.
>> How big a deal was it to you guys that
he's a four-year contributor on special
teams, too? like he keeps going up and
starting everywhere, but he stays being
a special teams contributor, too. Is
that for you guys?
>> Well, it always I mean, look, I mean, he
only got 48 guys dressing. So, somebody
I mean, even starters, I mean, they got
to play it. So, and his, you know, cuz
he's done it in the past. I think he's
had six special teams tackles, which is,
you know, for college pretty good. Um,
but he look, he's going to be a really
good football player. AJ's, he's
talented. He's a very I think you see
the boxy body and you automatically
think strong safety which of course he
can do. Um but he's better in deep field
than I think people give him credit for.
>> Just just to clarify I mean you kind of
have the need that you have is kind of
at strong safety technically. Is that a
fair statement
you see him possibly filling that need?
>> Yeah but you know talking to Lou and our
defensive staff one of the things they
wanted to be able to do was have
you know kind of be able to rock and
roll them. Um which Hunter can do also.
And look, we got a couple other vet
safeties in here can do a lot of jobs.
Like that's one of the things I think
getting CJ. Um, and then it allows us
some flexibility. Like AJ's got
flexibility. Willard's got flexibility.
Um, Jawan who we signed from Dallas got
flexibility. Owens got all these guys
got some flexibility to be able to play
different spots. And that also means as
a dime linebacker.
>> With CJ and the green dot, I guess going
through the process like what did you
see specifically with that aspect to his
game? Obviously, he did it a couple
years at Georgia
>> and and started as a true freshman in
wor like that's hard to do and and in
that defense like they stress him now.
They stress him mentally. So, he handled
that as a at a young age and it wasn't
too big for him. You know, even with I
mean I've been around I've been
fortunate now to be around some really
good ones like Anthony Walker is about
as smart as they come. Um and you know,
he picked it up pretty quick here. I
would I expect him to I expect CJ to do
the same thing.
>> There's a group of four or five
linebackers that were projected to go
somewhere in that second round group.
What made CJ stand out among the that
group of guys that you might have been
able to take in some other spots?
>> He is like he is fast and he is violent
like he's he is he's a f he is he is
fast and he's violent.
>> How confident were you that he would be
available at 53 when you decided to
trade back? Oh, look, you I mean, you
don't I mean, you you have a certain
degree of confidence they're going to be
there, but you've also got alternate
plans if he wasn't. But, uh, yeah, we
were we felt good when he was.
>> Did you guys go to his I know he didn't
run at the combine, but he did run here
recently coming off the injury. I'm sure
everything
>> Yeah, we were represented. Yeah.
>> Yeah, we were represented there. Yeah.
And we get the tape now, too. So you get
everything so quickly, workouts,
everything. I mean, it's downloaded
instantly.
>> With less guys testing nowadays, do you
guys rely more on like zebra technology
and all the GPS stuff to to get those
numbers?
>> Here's what's here's what's neat about
it. And our analytics team does a great
job with it. Like, all right, so you
have time speed. All right. Then does it
m does it match what we're getting, you
know, from the computer vision? Um, and
when it's a ma and when it's a match or
faster, that's a that's a good thing.
And with, you know, CJ, like it's
usually pretty easy on tape to see like
if a guy, you know, if they've got
bursting speed and, you know, then he
ran fast, you know, when he finally
worked out, um, and it matched. Same
thing with Same thing with Holly. He's,
you know, he's got good game, you know,
he's got good time speed, but also good
play speed. You talked about
>> you talked about him having the green
dot as a freshman and then you feel like
confident he can come in here and do
that. Is that something that some guys
do struggle with and the fact that he
did not what's that say?
>> Well, I mean it's it's like any rookie,
it's hard. Like I I don't care if you're
the second pick of the draft. Like it's
difficult. It's a it's a change. One of
the good things about you know the
system he's coming from is they put a
lot on the mic. I mean a lot of
adjustments on the mic. Um, so we think
he's going to be able to handle it
pretty well. Like we spent a lot of
time, I know BCH, our linebacker coach,
you know, we met with him at the
combine, but then we also had a long
Zoom with him and I know he grilled him
pretty hard and came came across you
raving about his IQ, which we taped it,
so I of course I watched it. It was
good.
>> When you look at the edge rusher
possibilities who were there when you
were gone the clock, what stuck out or
why did you come away with one?
a lot of it. I mean, like a lot of them
went early. Um, and then it was kind of
like what we had. I remember now, I
mean, we took Jaylen a year ago in the
second round and and we do think a lot
of him. I think he gets glossed over.
Um, but we do think there's some guys in
the, you know, fourth, fifth, sixth
round that's going to add a little juice
um, you know, as a rusher. So, we'll see
how it works out.
>> You think you'll do edge rusher after
the draft make better veteran?
>> Uh, we'll see. Yeah, we'll see. Yeah.
>> All right.
>> Awesome.
>> 118. How about the first round last
night?